（純一）はあ　はあ…
〈あの日〉
In order to avoid being late to the date she finally agreed to,
〈僕は　やっと取りつけた
デートの約束に遅れないように〉
〈１時間も早く　待ち合わせの
場所に駆けつけていた〉
I ran over to the meeting spot as early as I could that day.
〈そこには　クリスマスのせいなのか〉
Perhaps it was because it was Christmas?
The place was bustling with more couples than usual.
〈いつになく　カップルがあふれている〉
I was waiting for someone just like
everyone else, and it made me happy.
〈自分も同じように待ち合わせて
いることが　うれしかった〉
おかしいな
Weird...
I'm pretty sure I got the time and place right...
時間も待ち合わせ場所も合ってる
はずなんだけど…
That was Christmas Eve, two years ago.
〈２年前のクリスマスイブ〉
〈そのまま
彼女が現れることは　なかった〉
She never showed up to the date.
・～
I love you from my heart
I love you forever with you
SS
UTW Presents
Amagami
Ichinichi no hajimari to
１日の始まりと
From the start of the day
Owari ni wa itsumo soba ni
終わりにはいつも傍に
Till the end, you're by my side
Anata ga iru sonna mainichi
あなたがいる　そんな毎日
Every day is like this when you're here
Me wo samaseba attakai
目を覚ませば温かい
When I opened my eyes
Koohii irete matteru
コーヒー入れて待ってる
You were there with warm coffee
Anata no hidari ude ni dakitsuita
あなたの左腕に抱きついた
And so I clung onto your left arm
Aeru hi made yubiorikazoete ita
会える日まで指折り数えていた
I've been counting on my fingers the days until we meet again
Ima ja aenai hi no hou ga sukunai ne
今じゃ会えない日の方が少ないね
The days we meet now outnumber the days we don't
Konna shiawase dare ga yosou shita
こんな幸せ誰が予想した
Who would've thought that we'd find this happiness?
Anata to watashi ga sou
あなたと私がそう
You and I, yes
Koi wo shita
恋をした
We fell in love
Aishiteru anata no koto
愛してる　あなたのこと
I love you
Hajimete no kimochi yo
初めてのキモチよ
I've never felt like this before
Aishiteru zutto zutto
愛してる　ずっとずっと
I love you forever and ever
Kawaranai kimochi
変わらないキモチ
My feelings will never change
（美也）よし！
All right!
とっとっとっと
・（美也）え～ッ
にぃに　まだ起きてないの？
Huh?  Nii-nii still isn't up yet?
もうッ
Geez.
〈なぜ　２年前のあの時〉
Why didn't she come to our date two years ago?
〈彼女は来なかったんだろう？〉
I still don't know why.
〈その理由は今でも分からない〉
Ever since then, I've...
〈あれから　僕は…〉
にぃに！　も～ッ
また押し入れに　こもって
Nii-nii!
Geez, you shut yourself in the closet again?
早く起きないと
学校　遅刻しちゃうよ！
You're gonna be late for school if you don't get up now!
うんん…
うう…　にぃに！
Nii-nii!
うるさい
まだ僕は寝てたいんだ
Be quiet, I still want to sleep.
寒いし
まだ　ここから出たくない
It's cold and I don't wanna get out yet.
暖房　つければいいのに
All you needed to do was turn the heater on...
にっしっしし…
じゃあ　にぃにが出てこないなら
Well, if Nii-nii won't come out, I'll go in instead!
みゃーが　そっちに入るからね
にぃにの押し入れプラネタリウム
久しぶりに見たいし
It's been so long since I saw your closet planetarium too.
Hey, stop it, don't come in!
こら　やめろ　入るな！
This is a masterpiece I made for my own private enjoyment!
これは僕一人で観賞する
作品なんだ
Masterpiece?
作品って
蛍光ペンで描いただけじゃん
You just drew it with a highlighter!
うるさい！
みゃーも入るの！
S-Shut up!
I'm coming in too!
分かった　もう出るから
All right, I'll come out.
きゃッ
どうした？　美也
What's the matter, Miya?
・（美也）にぃにのバカ！
Nii-nii, you dummy!
にぃにと学校行くの久しぶりだね
そうか？
Nii-nii, it's been so long since we walked to school together.
Really?
だって　いつもみゃーのこと
置いていっちゃうじゃん
Yeah, Nii-nii, you usually go ahead and leave me behind.
美也は　すぐ道草　食うからな
That's because you keep taking your time, Miya.
それと　家の中じゃないんだから
「にぃに」　じゃないだろ
Also, we're not at home now, so don't call me "Nii-nii".
あッ　そっか　油断してた
ごめん　ごめん
Ah, right.
I forgot.  Sorry!
〈自分から
「学校ではベタベタしないでよ」〉
Weren't you the one who asked not to be so clingy at school?
〈とか言ってるくせに〉
あッ　お兄ちゃん
みゃー　先に行くね
Ah.  Onii-chan, see you later!
ああ
おっはよう！
Okay.
Morning!
（紗江）美也ちゃん　おはよう
Good morning, Miya-chan.
So she's Miya's friend.
美也の友達か
（梅原）美少女と並んで通学た～
朝からお熱いこと　この上ない
Walking to school with a hot chick.
There's nothing hotter than that in the morning.
冬の寒さも吹っ飛ぶなあ　橘！
It really blows away the winter cold, eh, Tachibana?
誰でしたっけ？
おッ　そうくるか　そうきちゃう？
Do I know you?
Oh?  This again?  This trick again?
妹と知ってて　からかうような
友達を持った覚えがないので
I don't recall having a friend who'd
tease me like that knowing she is my sister.
つれないねえ
せっかく新作が入ったから
You're no fun.
And I was going to share something new with you too...
持ってきてやったのに
あッ　例の写真集か？
Is that the photo album you were talking about?
I brought it with me for the sake of my best friend,
親しき友のためにと思って
持ってきたが
そう思っていたのは
俺だけとはねえ
but it looks like this friendship is one-sided.
ああ　よくみれば
小学校から一緒でクラスも一緒
Oh!  Now that I take a closer look,
aren't you the second son of a sushi chef,
すし屋の次男坊で僕の親友
梅原正吉じゃないか
my best friend who's been in my class
since elementary school, Umehara Masayoshi?
驚きの変わり身っぷりだな
You change personalities pretty quickly.
すまん
My bad.
いいってことよ
それでこそ　我が親友・橘純一
Don't worry about it.
Even so, you're still my best friend, Tachibana Junichi.
むしろ　その食い付きを待ってたぜ
In fact, I was just waiting for that reaction.
で　どうだった？
So how was it?
へっへ　まあまあ慌てなさんなって
Now now, no need to get that excited.
すごかったぜ
ホント？
It was awesome.
Really?
I see.
なるほどな～
それは　すごそうだ
It does sound pretty awesome.
I'll lend it to you, don't worry.
（梅原）ちゃんと貸してやるから
俺の大事な　お宝本
汚すなよ
Don't stain my precious book, though.
汚さないよ！
冗談だよ　冗談
Of course I won't!
I'm just kidding, man.
おッ！
どうした？
What's the matter?
森島先輩だよな？　あれ
Isn't she Morishima-senpai?
Oh come on, Hibiki!
（はるか）や～だ　もう響ったら
ふふふ…
絵になる人だよな～
写真集が　かすんじまうぜ
She's so beautiful, it's surreal.
She makes the photo album look dull.
Yeah, you're right.
ああ　そうだな
〈森島先輩
相変わらずキレイだよな〉
Morishima-senpai is beautiful, as always.
She also has a lot of fans at our school.
〈うちの学校には
森島先輩のファンが多い〉
〈こないだもクラスのヤツが
告白してフラれたらしい〉
If I remember correctly, she recently rejected some guy in our class.
おっと
早く行かないと遅刻しちまうぜ
Crap, let's hurry or we'll be late.
こんなことで遅刻してたら
商売　上がったりだ
You're not getting anything if we're late because of this!
Let's run!
急ごうぜ
ああ
Okay.
Morishima Haruka Arc
Chapter 1
Longing
（麻耶）そろそろ　今年の創設祭が
近づいてきました
This year's Founder's Festival is fast approaching.
そこで　クラスの
実行委員を決めないといけません
Thus, we need to decide on
committee members from this class.
誰か　立候補はありませんか？
Any volunteers?
（詞）高橋先生
誰も立候補がないようなら
Takahashi-sensei.
If no one wants to do it, I will.
私が　やりましょうか？
・（麻耶）絢辻さん→
Ayatsuji-san?
あなた　クラス委員の
仕事もやってくれているし
You're already working as the class representative.
掛け持ちになるけど大丈夫？
Are you sure you want another position?
（詞）はい　クラス委員の仕事は→
Yes.  I don't really have much work left as
class representative now that it's November.
もう１１月ですから
あまりありませんし
クリスマスにある
創設祭までの短い期間ですから
Also, it's only a short while until the
Founder's Festival, which is around Christmas.
そう　じゃあ　お願いするわね
はい
I see.
In that case, please do your best.
Yes.
Now, we're halfway through November...
（麻耶）さて
１１月も残り半分ですが…
〈絢辻さん〉
Ayatsuji-san always does the things no one else wants to do.
〈いつも人が嫌がるようなことを
進んで引き受けてる〉
〈マジメだよなあ〉
She's really hardworking.
あッ
Okay.
はあ…
おう大将　昼飯にしようぜ
Sup, boss.
Let's have lunch.
そうだな
今日はパンでも買ってくるか？
Sure.
Should we buy some bread today?
Wait right there!
（薫）ちょっと待った
何だよ　薫？
What's the matter, Kaoru?
むふ～
今日は私もパンにしようと思って
I was thinking of having bread today too.
じゃあ　棚町も一緒に行くか？
Wanna tag along then, Tanamachi?
ちっちっちっ　一緒に買いにいく
だけじゃ　つまらないじゃない
It's no fun if we all go together.
Let's have a game of rock-paper-scissors!
ジャンケンしましょうよ
Whoever loses has to buy bread for all three of us.  What do you think?
ジャンケンで負けた人が
勝った人達の分まで
買いに行くってので　どう？
Oh, I see.
なるほど
いくよ～
Here we go!
ジャンケン　ポン！
Rock, paper, scissors!
はあ
私　焼きそばパンとチョココロネ！
I want Yakisoba bread and a chocolate cornet!
I want a pork sandwich and a red bean paste bun.
俺はカツサンドとアンパンな
はいはい
Yeah, yeah.
うわッ　こりゃ大変だ
Wow, this looks bad.
うん？
ああ　１年生かな？
She must be a freshman.
この状態でパンを買うには
コツがあるからな
There's a trick to buying bread at times like this.
よし！
All right.
何が　ほしいのかな？
（紗江）えッ
What would you like?
パンを買いにきたんじゃないの？
You're here to buy bread, right?
はい…　あの
Yes...
U-Um...
I'd like a milk and one of the sweet breads...
牛乳と何か甘いパンを…
よし　僕に任せといて
All right, leave it to me.
Here you go.  Milk and something sweet.
はい　牛乳と甘いやつ
あッ　ありがとうございます
T-Thank you.
適当に選んじゃったけど大丈夫？
I just chose whatever.  You okay with that?
大丈夫です
Yes.
うん？
あッ…
Um...
あの…　お金
H-How much?
ああ　お金ね　３６０円だったよ
Oh, the price?
It was 360 yen.
じゃッ　今度は頑張ってね
Do your best next time.
〈さっきの子
顔を真っ赤にして慌ててたな〉
That girl just then...
She was all red and flustered.
〈余計なことしない方が
よかったのかな？〉
Maybe I shouldn't have offered to help.
わッ　うわ～ッ！
テテテ…
（はるか）ねえ　君
Hey, you.
ヤバ　早く拾わなきゃ
Crap.  I'd better pick them all up...
そこの大食いの君！
You there with the big appetite!
えッ？
もッ　森島先輩
M-Morishima-senpai.
Oh?  Have we met before?
ありゃ
どこかで会ったことあったっけ？
はい　これ
落としたよ　大食い君
Here you go.
You dropped it, big appetite-kun.
あッ…　すみません
S-Sorry.
ありがとうございます
Thank you.
う～ん
あッ…
あなた
はッ　はい
Hey.
Y-Yes?
かわいらしい目をしてる
はッ？
You have adorable eyes.
Huh?
で　どこかで会ったこと
あったっけ？
So did we meet somewhere before?
えッ…　いやあ
No...
I see.  That makes sense.
そっか　そうだよね
I usually remember people I've met before.
私　一度会った人って
結構　覚えているはずだから
ねえ　君
さっき１年生の子に
Hey, weren't you the guy who bought bread for that freshman?
パンを買ってあげてた子だよね？
えッ　ああ　はい
Um, yeah.
I did...
そうですけど…
グッド　君って優しいんだね
Good.  You're really nice.
じゃッ　もう転ばないようにね
Bye.  Make sure you don't fall over again!
〈森島先輩と話しちゃったよ〉
I got to talk with Morishima-senpai...
〈ああ　先輩の　いいにおいが
まだ残ってる〉
I can still smell her wonderful scent.
・（梨穂子）おーい　おーい→
Hey!
Hey.
おーい！
うわッ！
Hey.
梨穂子
純一　どうしたの？
Rihoko.
Junichi, what's the matter?
Nothing at all.
いや　何でもないよ
ふ～ん…　ねえ
何？
Hey.
What?
それ　純一が全部　食べるの？
Are you really going to eat all of that?
そんなわけないだろう
Of course not.
だよね
I guess!
梨穂子なら　これくらい
一人で食べちゃいそうだよな
You'd probably be able to finish all of this yourself though, Rihoko.
えーッ　さすがに
そんなに食べられないよ
Huh?  I definitely can't eat that much.
You were so slow I thought I was gonna die of hunger!
あんたが遅いから　おなかすいて
死んじゃうかと思ったわよ
（梅原）まったく　何してたんだよ？
Geez, what were you doing?
しかたないだろ
いろいろあったんだよ　いろいろ
It's not my fault.
Lots of things happened.
いろいろって何よ？
Like what?
（詞）食事中　ごめんなさい
Sorry to disturb you while you're eating,
ちょっと　いいかしら？
but do you have a moment?
Ayatsuji-san, what is it?
絢辻さん　何？
高橋先生に　みんなの進路表を
Takahashi-sensei asked me to collect
everyone's guidance papers by today,
今日中に集めるように
言われてたんだけど
まだ出してないの　橘君だけなの
but you're the only one who hasn't turned one in yet, Tachibana-kun.
今日　帰るまでに
出してもらえるかな？
Could you turn it in before you leave today?
あッ　ごめん　忘れてた
後で出すよ
Sorry, I forgot about it.
I'll turn it in later.
じゃあ　よろしくね
Okay, I'd appreciate it.
（梅原・薫）ぷは～ッ！
（チャイム）
（詞）はい　ありがとう
Okay, thanks.
じゃあ　先生に提出しておくわね
I'll turn it in to the teacher.
待たせてごめんね
ううん　大丈夫
Sorry you had to wait for me.
No, it's fine.
どうしたの？
Is something wrong?
Ah, I was just wondering where Umehara went.
梅原が
どこに行ったかなと思ってさ
カバンが机にあるから　まだ帰った
わけじゃないと思うんだけど
His bag is still at his desk, so I don't think he went home yet.
・（詞）梅原君なら　さっき図書室に
行くようなこと言ってたわよ
If you're looking for Umehara-kun,
he said something about going to the library.
ホント？　まだ昼のパン代を
もらってないから取り立てないと
Really?
He hasn't paid me back yet for the bread earlier,
so I need to bug him about that.
Is that so?  You should definitely talk to him about that.
あら　それはしっかり
取り立てた方が　いいわね
Yeah.  Well, I'll go look in the library.
うん　じゃあ
ちょっと図書室を見てくるよ
I also need to get a good look at his new photo album!
〈新作の写真集も　きっちり
拝ませてもらわないとな〉
わッ
きゃッ！
イッタ～
Ow...
すッ　すみません！
S-Sorry!
あッ　森島先輩？
Morishima-senpai?
あら　君は　お昼の大食い君？→
Oh?  Aren't you the one with the big appetite from lunchtime?
ナイス　タイミング！
えッ
Nice timing!
さっきは　すいませんでした
Sorry about that.
人を捜してたので
キョロキョロしてたから
I got impatient looking around for someone...
Don't worry about it.
ううん　いいのよ
I wasn't looking where I was going either.
私も　よそ見しちゃってたから
Anyway, you're doing me a big favor by carrying those books.
それより　本を運んでもらって
助かっちゃったわ
Is it okay, though?
でもいいの？
誰か捜してたんでしょ？
Weren't you looking for someone?
ああ　いいんです
ちょっと用事があったんですけど
Oh, it's fine.
I had some business with him, but it can wait.
別に急ぎませんから
〈まあ　森島先輩の荷物持ちより
大事な用事は〉
Well, there aren't many things more important than carrying stuff for Morishima-senpai.
〈そうそう　ないからな〉
あッ　響ちゃん
Hibiki-chan!
（響）はるか　どうしたの？
はあ？
What is it, Haruka?
見て見て　図書室に　かわいい犬の
写真集がこんなにあったの
Look, look!
They actually had all these
photo books of cute dogs at the library!
借りたのは　いいけど
持ってくるのが大変だったから
Borrowing them wasn't that bad,
but carrying them around is tough.
手伝ってもらっちゃった
So I got him to help.
はあ…
どうも
Hello.
Sorry about that.
ごめんなさい　はるかが
迷惑かけちゃったみたいね
It seems Haruka has troubled you.
ああ　いえ
別に大したことありませんから
Oh, it's fine.
It wasn't a big deal.
どうせ　暇ですし
I was free too.
はるか
ちゃんと彼に　お礼言いなさい
Haruka, go ahead and thank him properly.
Okay.
うん　ありがとう
えっと…
Thanks, uh...
That's right, I still don't know your name.
そうだ　君の名前
まだ聞いてなかったよね
ああ　そうですね
Oh, you're right.
I-I'm T-Tachibana Junichi from Class 2-A.
ぼッ　僕は２年Ａ組
たッ　橘純一です
ありがとう　橘純一君
Thanks, Tachibana Junichi-kun.
I-It's fine.
いッ　いいえ
あきれた
I'm shocked.
名前も知らないのに　こんな
荷物持ちを頼んだの？　はるか
You didn't even know his name, and yet you made him carry all this, Haruka?
ふっふふ
名前は知らなかったけど
I may not have known his name,
but I knew I could count on Tachibana-kun.
橘君なら
頼んでも大丈夫って分かってたよ
えッ
どうして？
Why?
That's because Tachibana-kun's really nice.
だって　橘君　優しいもん
ふふふ…
Yo, Tachibana!  Check this out!
おい　橘！　これ見ろよ
They actually kept photo book treasures like these hidden away at the library!
図書室に　こんなお宝写真集が
眠ってたんだぜ
情報を聞いて　すぐさま
ゲットしてきたってわけさ
I went to get them right after I heard about them.
多分　卒業した先輩の…
One of the former students probably left it behi-
Uh, what's the matter with you?
お前　どうしたんだ？
僕　また　頑張ってみようかな
Maybe I'll try again.
はあ？　何を頑張るんだ？
Huh?  Try what again?
〈２年前に失った感情を〉
Those feelings I lost two years ago...
〈僕は　このとき
取り戻そうとしていた〉
I wanted to find them again.
おい　どうした？
Hey, what's wrong?
〈森島先輩〉
Morishima-senpai.
〈校内のアイドルのような
高根の花だけど〉
She's the school idol and probably unreachable,
Y-You okay?
〈でも僕は先輩のことが…〉
but I think I'm falling for her.
Hey-
おい　って…
顔　赤いじゃねえか
Whoa, your face is all red!
Is it a cold?  Are you not feeling well?
カゼか？　体調悪いのか？
〈２年前の　あのクリスマス〉
Two years ago on Christmas, my heart was broken.
〈僕は失恋をした〉
〈もう　あんな思いはしたくないと
臆病になってた〉
I became afraid of having to go through that again.
〈でも　今年こそは
幸せなクリスマスを！〉
But this year I'll definitely have a blessed Christmas!
〈だけど森島先輩は
高根の花だからな〉
Unfortunately, Morishima-senpai is way out of my league.
〈実際　図書室で会ってから
もう何日も会ってないし〉
In fact, I haven't seen her since that incident at the library.
〈そう簡単に
うまくいくわけないか〉
I guess there's no way things would go that smoothly.
（はるか）私も入れて～！→
Let me play too!
えいッ！
えッ→
森島先輩？
Morishima-senpai?!
へへへ…　えいえいッ！
Morishima-senpai?
森島先輩！？
ああッ　うッ…
What's the matter, Morishima-senpai?
どうしたんですか？　森島先輩
うふふ　あのね
Here I was thinking there were a bunch of kids
playing leapfrog, until I saw you with them.
馬跳びをしてる
子達がいるなあと思ったら
その中に橘君がいたから
私も交ぜてもらっちゃおうと
思ったの
So I thought I'd join in too!
You came out of nowhere, so you really surprised me.
いきなりだったから
びっくりしましたよ
橘君だったら
飛び入りでもＯＫかなあと思って
I thought you'd be fine with me jumping in, Tachibana-kun.
だって　橘君　優しいから→
I mean, it's because you're really nice.
馬跳びなんて
久しぶりにしたわ～
It's been so long since I played leapfrog!
小学校の頃は　男子に交ざって
一緒にやってたのよ
I used to play it with the boys from my elementary school.
へえ　そうなんですか？
Oh, really?
あッ　お兄ちゃん
Huh, Onii-chan?
あッ　美也
Oh, Miya.
美也　こちら森島先輩
Miya, this is Morishima-senpai.
知ってるだろ？
うん
I'm sure you've heard of her.
Yeah...
先輩　妹の美也です
Senpai, this is my sister, Miya.
Good afternoon.
こんにちは
Your sister's adorable.
かわいい妹さんね
そうですか？
You think so?
生意気な　ばっかりなんですよ
She's nothing but cheeky.
午後の授業　教室移動だから
もう行くね
I have to switch classrooms for
my afternoon classes, so I'm off.
おい　美也！
Hey, Miya!
どうしたんだ？　あいつ
What's wrong with her?
嫌われちゃったかな？
She probably hates me now.
あ～ん
でもかわいいわ　美也ちゃん
Oh, Miya-chan is so cute though.
ネコちゃんみたい
そうですか？
She's just like a kitty.
Really?
ええ　仲良くなって
一緒に買い物行ったり
Yeah.
I want to get closer to her, so we can go shopping and take baths together!
おふろに入ったりしたいなあ
えッ　おふろですか？
Eh, b-baths?!
Yep!  It'll be fun!
うん！　きっと楽しいわ
Morishima-senpai and Miya together in the bath...
〈森島先輩と美也が
一緒におふろ…〉
Hey, Haru-chan.
《（美也）ねえ　はるちゃん
バストアップ体操ってこれでいいの？》
Is this all I need to do to make my boobs bigger?
《（はるか）うん　そうそう→》
Yep, that's right.
Oh, but you should do it like this...
《でも　ちょっと　この辺をこう…》
《（美也）こう？》
《うん　うまいわ　みゃー》
Like this?
Yep.  You're good, Miya!
But this kinda tickles.
《でもこれ
ちょっと　くすぐったいね》
《そうね》
Yeah.
A-Anyway, I'll have to ask Miya
why she wasn't very happy later.
〈とッ　とにかく　美也が
何で不機嫌そうだったのか〉
〈後で聞かないとな〉
美也！
Miya!
あッ　お兄ちゃん
どうしたの？
Oh, Onii-chan.
What's the matter?
Why were you so rude to Morishima-senpai this lunch break?
お前　昼休みに森島先輩の前で
何で
あんなに無愛想にしたんだよ？
先輩
お前のこと　かわいいって言って
She said you were cute and wanted to get closer to you.
仲良くなりたかったみたいだぞ
Yeah, right.
あっそう　仲良くなりたいのは
お兄ちゃんの方でしょ
Aren't you the one who wants to get closer to her, Onii-chan?
森島先輩　美人だし
スタイルもいいもんね！
Since Morishima-senpai is really pretty and has a nice body?!
What's wrong with you, getting all lovestruck?!
何よ！
デレデレ鼻の下　のばしちゃってさ
Nii-nii, you dummy!
バカにぃに！
あッ
It's Morishima-senpai...
〈森島先輩…〉
〈キレイだ〉
She's beautiful.
（はるかのクシャミ）
先輩　これどうぞ
Senpai, take this.
Tachibana-kun...
橘君…　使い捨てカイロ？
Is that a disposable hand warmer?
カゼ　ひいちゃいますよ
You'll catch a cold otherwise.
ふふ　ありがとう
Thanks.
You're really nice.
優しいのね
何してたんですか？
うーん
What were you doing?
Well...
あのね　水を見てたの
I was looking at the water.
水…　ですか？
The... water?
うん
私　水を見るのが好きなの
Yeah.
I like looking at water.
Like the sea, the river...
海とか　川とか　噴水とかね
...and the fountain.
いいですね
何となくですけど
That sounds nice.
I think it suits you somehow, Morishima-senpai.
森島先輩には
似合ってる気がします
うふッ　そういうふうに
言ってくれたのって
You and Hibiki are probably the only ones who've said that to me.
響と橘君だけかも
You're so nice.  Why, you!
優しいのね　このこの～
そッ　そんなことないです
T-That's not it at all.
（はるか）そうなの？
じゃあ　私にだけ優しいのかな？
Really?
Then are you saying you're only this nice towards me?
もしかして　私のこと　好きなの？
Could it be that...
...you like me?
Just kidding.
なーんちゃって
あッ
N-No, well...
いや…　そんな
ふふ…　そうよね
I see.
That's a shame.
残念
It's so warm...
あったか～い
I like you.
好きです
えッ？
僕　森島先輩のことが好きです！
I like you, Morishima-senpai!
本気？
はい　本気です！
Really?
Yes, really!
そうなんだ
I see.
ふ～ん
Hmm.
橘君って
思ってたより　男らしいんだね
You're more of a man than I thought, Tachibana-kun.
そうですか？
うん
Really?
Yeah.
ちょっと　びっくりしちゃった
You kinda surprised me.
ありがとう
すごく　うれしい
Thanks.
I'm really happy.
Senpai...
先輩…
でもダメ
But no.
えッ
私
年上で
頼り甲斐のある人が好みなの
I prefer someone who's reliable and older than me.
Is that so?
そうなんですか？
うん
Yeah.
Well, see you, Tachibana-kun.
それじゃあ　またね　橘君
Oh, and thanks for the hand warmer.
あッ　カイロありがとう
すごく　あったかいよ
It's really warm.
うん？
橘君？
Tachibana-kun?
〈あれ？　僕〉
Huh?
Was I rejected?
〈フラれちゃったのか？〉
〈ていうか　告白しちゃった？〉
Wait, did I really confess to her?
No, no.  That wasn't a confession.
〈いやいや　告白じゃないよ〉
〈でも…〉
But...
とりあえず帰るか…
I guess I'll go home for now.
Nii-nii, you're home?
・（美也）にぃに　帰ったの？→
I have some steamed meat buns.  Do you want some?
まんま肉まん　あるよ　食べる？
うん？
寒い
It's cold.
入るか…
Guess I'll go in.
・～
Kawaii sore dake de
かわいいそれだけで
"Cute".  With just that one word
Muchuu de nadetaku naru urunda hitomi
夢中で撫でたくなる潤んだ瞳
I'm in a daze, and I want to rub my teary eyes
Jarete iru toki wa
じゃれている時は
When you were flirting with me
Natsuite iru dake da to
なついているだけだと
You were just being friendly
Omotteta n da
思ってたんだ
At least, that's what I thought
Koi no hajimari nante
恋の始まりなんて
The beginning of a romance
Yohou hazure no tenki mitai
予報外れの天気みたい
is like a missed weather forecast
Ameagari no niji no sora ni te nobasou
雨上がりの虹の空に手伸ばそう
I stretch my hands towards the rainbow-filled sky after the rain
Kimi no tonari wa sunao na
君の隣は素直な
Because when I'm by your side
Kimochi ni nareru kara
気持ちになれるから
I can be honest with myself
Kizuita kimi no koto omou
気付いた君の事想う
I've realized that when I think about you
Jikan wa mune no oku ga konnani takanaru koto
時間は胸の奥がこんなに高鳴る事
My heart starts to pound so much
Kinou yume no naka ni
昨日夢の中に
In my dream last night
Mata kimi ga dete kita
また君が出てきた
You appeared again
Preview
Next episode preview...
Nii-nii, you're not having any steamed meat buns?
I don't want any.
What?!
But they're so good!
The juices overflowing in your mouth,
and the chewiness and savory taste of the meat...
Good for you, Miya.
You seem happy.
Next episode: "Approach".
Next Episode
Approach
Nii-nii, the sun will rise again tomorrow!
Everyone, p-please look forward to the next episode.